EHAB **MOHAMED**

I have more than 12 years of experience in software development, I involved in the full-stack development of web applications using C#, NodeJs, Golang,...etc for the back-end and Angular|S for the front-end. Beside that, I was publishing researches in the topics of text clustering and feature selection mainly using R as a part of the Master Degree.

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR DEVELOPER ▼ FREELANCING

since April 2020, Using Golang and Elasticsearch to build insight website. Also, involved in other projects using C#, Angular 8, NodeJS, Typescript and ElectronJS.

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ▼ IGNITE (REMOTE – NETHERLANDS)

October 2016 - December 2019, Build new features and maintenance websites, services and tools for job vacancies websites in Netherlands and other countries.

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER **▼ COMEX**

October 2014 - October 2016, Responsible for building a web application for reporting, sales, purchases, warehouses, and real estate.

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER **▼ HINDAWI**November 2012 - October 2014 , Responsible for Back office website for publishing books and articles.

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ▼ MENA SOFTWARE (REMOTE – BULGARIA)

February 2012 - November 2012, Developing Games Portals, Administrations and Gates websites.

DEVELOPER **▼ TEBAS**, TRUE TECHNOLOGY

2004 - 2009, Developed a web and desktop applications for Personnel (HR, Time Attendance, Payroll), Hospital, POS and Restaurant.

EDUCATION

MASTER OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Major in Text Clustering and Data Mining, Cairo University.

HIGHER DIPLOMA

Major in Computer Science, Cairo University.

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE

Major in Accounting, Ain Shams University.

SKILLS

R language

Python, Numpy, Pandas, matplotlib,